Guide to the Brooklyn For Peace records 2016.026
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 5: Subject Files, 1986-2017; 7 Linear Feet in 13 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box.
  - May 1st Coalition for Worker and Immigrant Rights, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 6, Flat file folder 1)
  - Military Families Speak Out, 2007-2013 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Military Recruitment in Schools Opt Out, 2005-2009 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Before you Enlist! The Real Deal on Joining the Military DVD, 2006 (Box 43)
  - Miller, Gifford, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Muslim Consultative Network, 2011-2014 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Muslim Solidraity Committee and Project - SALAM, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - NACLA Report on the Americas, 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - National Agenda for Peace in El Salvador, 1989-2009 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - National Lawyers Guild, 2006-2010 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - National Peace Institute Foundation, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - National Priorities Project, 2009-2012 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Native American Organizations, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - New Profile, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - New York Bill of Rights Defense Campaign, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - New York Blood Center, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - New York City Coalition for Darfur, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - New York City Council, 2002-2015 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - New York City Grassroots Media Coaliton, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - New York City Organizations, 1985-2015 (Box 35, Folder 5, Box 37, Folder 7)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2002-2010 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - New York Coalition for Peace and Justice, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - New York Council for the Humanities, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - New York Institute for Human Development, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - New York Not in Our Name, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - New York Non Profits - NPCC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - New York Peace Film Festival, 2013-2016 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - New York Police Department Stop and Frisk Policy Policing, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - New York Society for Ethical Culture, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - New Yorkers Against Gun Violence, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Nhojj, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York, 1988-2010 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Norman Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - North American Organizations, 1987-2011 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - North Star Fund, 1989-2017 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Disarmament, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Policy Organizations, 1985-2014 (Box 25, Folder 7, Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Nuke Busters, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Obama, Barack, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Occupy, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - On May 12, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - One Million Moms for Gun Control, 2001-2013 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - One Nation Working Together, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Owens, Major, 2000-2006 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Palestine Children's Relief Fund, 2009-2014 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Palestine Solidarity Committee, circa 1990s (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Parents for Student Success, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Park Slope United Methodist Church, 2003-2016 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Park Slope Food Coop, circa 2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Parents and Teachers for Social Responsibility, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Party for the People, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Pax Christi Metro New York, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Peace Action, 1998-2015 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Peace Action New York State, 2002-2016 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Peace and Planet, 2001-2015 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Peace Development Fund, 1984-1988 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Peace Dividend Campaign, circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Peace in the Middle East, 1990-2007 (Box 26, Folder 20, Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Peace New York City, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Peace Organizations, 1987-2013 (Box 35, Folder 6, Box 37, Folder 11, Flat file folder 1)
  - Peace Resource Project, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Peaceful Tomorrows, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - PENGON Anti-Apartheid Wall Campaign, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - People's Climate Movement New York, 2017 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Physicians for Human Rights, 2000-2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Physicians for a National Health Program - PNHP, 2000-2016 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1998-2013 (Box 27, Folder 7, Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Police and Resistance, 2002-2015 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Police Violence, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Politicians and Political Organizations, 1991-2014 (Box 27, Folder 10, Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Project Abolition, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Police Reform Organizing Project - P.R.O.P, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The Public Eye, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - The Rebuilding Alliance, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Redevelopment of Downtown Brooklyn, 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Religious Organizations, 2001-2015 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Resist, 1986-2014 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Revolutionary Association of the Women of Afghanistan, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Riverside Church, 2001-2010 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Sane Energy Project, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Save Darfur, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Save Jeju Now, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Save Our Streets Crown Heights - S.O.S, 2010-2012 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - School of the Americas Watch - SOA, 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Schumer, Charles, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - The Shalom Center, circa 2005 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Shut Down Indian Point, circa 2005 (Box 27, Folder 20, Flat file folder 1)
  - Socialist Organizations, 2011-2013 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Solarz, Stephen J, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 23, Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Solidarity Action for Human Rights - SAHR, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Solitary Confinement, 2003-2012 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Solidarity for Peace and Reunification of Korea, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Staten Island Navel Homeport Plan, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Stop AIPAC, 2006-2008 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Stop the Pipeline, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Student Nuclear Action Project - SNAP!, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Draft Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement - Volume III, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 4-6)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Final Environmental Impact Statement - Volume II, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Final Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement - Volume IV, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Final Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement - Volume IV, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Hawaii Documents, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Naval Weapons Evaluation Facility, 1965-1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Public Hearing, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
  - Surface Action Group Homeporting - Supplemental Public Hearing, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Syed Fahad Hashmi Case, 2007-2010 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Syria - Military Intervention, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Theater for the New City, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Tikkun Community, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Toronto Coalition to Stop the War, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Towns, Edolphus "Ed", 1990-2011 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Unify the Hood, Heal the Hood, circa 2005 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists, 2008-2010 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - United Daughter of Shaba-Sheba, 2003-2006 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - United for Peace and Justice, 2002-2016 (Box 30, Folder 32-33, Box 37, Folder 15)
  - United National Antiwar Coalition - UNAC, 2010-2012 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - United Nations, 1996-2016 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - United Nations Children's Fund - UNICEF, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - The United Nations Refugee Agency (UNHCR), 2016 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - United States Campaign to Ban Landmines, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - The United States Institute of Peace, 1986-2008 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - United States Labor Against the War, 2001-2015 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - United States Servas, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - UP Rose, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Uranium Policy Organizations, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Velaquez, Nydia, 2002-2015 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Veterans for Peace, 2007-2016 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam Agent Orange Relief and Responsibility Campaign, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Violence and the Media, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Violence and the Media, 1988-1994 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Visions of Peace and Justice in Israel - Palestine, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - War Organizations, 1991-2017 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - War Resisters League, 1988-2016 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - WBAI, 2000-2009 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - We Are All Brooklyn - WAAB, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Reform, 1997-1999 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Women for Afghan Women, 2003-2008 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Women in Black, circa 2009 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 2000-2013 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Women's Organizations, 2000-2016 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - World Can't Wait, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Young Koreans United of U.S.A., 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Series 6: Petitions, 1985-2015; 1 Linear Feet in 2 and half manuscript boxes
  Material in this series consists of petitions signed and turned in to BFP to support their efforts to bring an end to local and international war and conflicts. These petitions contain biographical information including names, addresses, and phone numbers of the signees. Subjects that are well represented in this series include the War in Iraq, the Israel-Palestine conflict, biased New York Police Department practices, and a Nuclear-free New York City
  Materials have been grouped by subject and are arranged alphabetically.
  - Abolition 2000 - Missiles to Sunflowers (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Restricted until 2030.
  - A Citizens' Humanitarian Pledge - Support for All Iraqis, circa 2003 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Community Access Television - Democracy Now!, circa 2008 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn's Peace Petition - Stop the War in Iraq, circa 2003 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn Says a Resounding NO to War Against Iraq, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
  - Brooklyn Says No! - No Nuclear Missiles in Our Harbor, circa 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
  - Children's Rights Are Not Negotiable - Resist Welfare or Medicaid "reform" Bill, circa 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Restricted until 2028.
  - Declare New York City a Mayor's City of Peace, 2015 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - End the Corporate Invasion of Iraq, circa 2008 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - End the Humanitarian Crisis in Gaza, circa 2008 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - For Israel and Palestine - Against Injustice and Violence, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - For Israel and Palestine - Against Violence and Hate, circa 2005 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - For Peace and Justice in the Middle East - Israel and Palestine, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Restricted until 2032.
  - Independent Inquiry into the Reasons for War with Iraq, circa 2005 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Israel-Palestine Peace Campaign - Roadmap or Cul-De-Sac?, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Iraq Pledge of Resistance - To Stop the War Against Iraq, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Iraq Peace Pledge - A Project of the Campaign of Conscience, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
  - No United States Military Intervention in Syria, circa 2014 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Peaceful Resolution in Iran - Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Pledge of Resistance - Middle East War, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - PROP - End Biased New York Police Department Policies and Practices, circa 2010 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Protest Israel's Attempt to Limit Foreign Witnesses, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Solve the Syrian Conflict, circa 2011 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Stop the Genocide in Darfur, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Support Diplomacy, Give Peace a Chance, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Support the Kennedy-Byrd Resolution, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Time to Abolish Nuclear Weapons, circa 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - To the FCC - Regarding Broadcast Ownership, circa 2013 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - United States Campaign to End the Israeli Occupation, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Voices from Brooklyn - Halt the War and Promote Peace, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Voices from Brooklyn - Halt the War and Promote Peace, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Vote NO on the War on Iraq - Give United Nations Weapons Inspectors a Chance, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
  - We Say No to Any United States Attack Against Pakistan, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 5)